<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>

    <string name="title_one">Plan a Trip</string>
    <string name="title_two">Top Attractions</string>
    <string name="title_three">Explore Cities</string>
    <string name="india">India</string>
    <string name="titleState">Maharashtra</string>

    <string-array name="placeName">
        <item>Mumbai</item>
        <item>Ajanta Caves</item>
        <item>Mahabaleshwar</item>
        <item>Panchghati</item>
        <item>Rajmachi</item>
        <item>Kashid</item>
        <item>Alibag</item>
        <item>Ganpatipule</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="placeImage">
        <item>https://www.holidify.com/images/bgImages/MUMBAI.jpg</item>
        <item>https://cdn.pixabay.com/photo/2020/03/31/09/37/ajanta-caves-4986845_1280.jpg</item>
        <item>https://cdn.pixabay.com/photo/2019/08/26/15/33/visapur-fort-4432061_1280.jpg</item>
        <item>https://www.holidify.com/images/bgImages/PANCHGANI.jpg</item>
        <item>https://www.holidify.com/images/bgImages/RAJMACHI.jpg</item>
        <item>https://www.holidify.com/images/bgImages/KASHID.jpg</item>
        <item>https://www.holidify.com/images/bgImages/ALIBAG.jpg</item>
        <item>https://www.holidify.com/images/bgImages/GANAPATIPULE.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="placeDescription">
        <item>Labeled with multiple titles such as \'Financial capital of India\',
            \'The Maximum City\', \'Land of Bollywood\', \'The dream City\' and much more, Mumbai
            is Maharashtra\'s capital and India\'s most populous city which has
            multiple faces making it all things to all people.</item>
        <item>Ajanta and Ellora caves are considered to be one of the most important tourist
            destinations in the world owing to the magnificent paintings
            of Ajanta and well carved sculptures of Ellora.</item>
        <item>A hill town in Western Ghats, apart from its strawberries, Mahabaleshwar is
            also well known for its numerous rivers, magnificent cascades and majestic peaks.</item>
        <item>Deriving its name from the five hills surrounding it, Panchgani is a popular hill station near
            Mahabaleshwar famous for its various sunset/sunrise points and scenic valley view.</item>
        <item>Rajmachi has two fortified peaks - Shrivardhan and Manaranjan forts,
            located near two famous hills of Lonavala and Khandala.</item>
        <item>A Beach town, popular for its white sand and blue seas situated in Konkan region of Maharashtra,
            Kashid is the perfect destination for a quiet weekend getaway from Mumbai.</item>
        <item>A popular weekend getaway destination for Mumbai folks, Alibaug is a coastal town in the Konkan
            region well known for its sandy beaches, clean water and fresh, unpolluted air.</item>
        <item>Beach town on the Konkan coastline, Ganpatipule has temples of Lord Ganesha as major
            attractions apart from the beautiful virgin beaches.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="foodName">
        <item>Pav Bhaji</item>
        <item>Vada Pav</item>
        <item>Puran Poli</item>
        <item>Misal Pav</item>
        <item>Aamras</item>
        <item>Poha</item>
        <item>Ragda Pattice</item>
        <item>Modak</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="foodImage">
        <item>https://ratlamee.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/Cheese-Pav-Bhaji-1.jpg</item>
        <item>https://img4.nbstatic.in/tr:w-500/56ab0c3d0b04512cde6af3ff.png</item>
        <item>https://www.archanaskitchen.com/images/archanaskitchen/1-Author/Bela-Dholakia/puran-poli-recipe-with-toor-dal-and-chana-dal.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/94/Misal_Pav_from_Maharashtra.JPG</item>
        <item>https://www.cookwithkushi.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/IMG_0408_.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/57/Cooked_Poha.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.shutterstock.com/image-photo/ragda-pattice-mumbai-street-foodchat-600w-1073918144.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/22/Ukdiche_Modak.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="foodDescription">
        <item>Amchi Maharashtra food is incomplete without this dish which has come to be
            synonymous to the state! Fresh and thick slices of bread, smothered in butter
            served with a delicious mix of moderately spiced vegetables. This lip-smacking
            dish has won the heart of every Indian!</item>
        <item>Vada Pav can easily be called the Indian version of a burger! A delicious,
            spicy, deep-fried patty made of potato is squeezed between a thick slice of bread,
            similar to a burger bun. Between the vada (patty) and pav (bread) a spicy mix of spices
            and salt is sprinkled and garnished with a fried, salted green chilli. Sounds perfect,
            isn\'t it? It\'s an all-day snack and is extremely popular among Maharashtrians</item>
        <item>This delectable food item is a sweet version of the loving parantha.
            The stuffing is made from jaggery (gur), yellow gram (chana) dal, plain flour,
            cardamom powder and ghee (clarified butter). It is a popular dish in festive
            occasions and also can be eaten at any time of the day.
            A tasty dessert does not need anyone\'s permission to be eaten!</item>
        <item>Misal Pav is quintessentially from Pune and is one of the most popular
            Maharashtrian breakfast, snack or even brunch. It is a street food popularly found
            in Mumbai. It has a spicy and tangy lentil curry which is made with moth beans
            and is served with Pav bread. At times, it is eaten with yoghurt to lessen the spice.
            Although it is a breakfast food but Maharashtrians enjoy it at time of the day.</item>
        <item>Summer season is all about mangoes and aamrus is one of the favourite mango servings
            in Maharashtra. The aamras is made from the mango pulp and is thick in texture.
            The pulp is extracted by hand and it takes not more than 30 minutes to prepare.</item>
        <item>This chai-time snack which is made out of flattened rice is a favourite among
            every Maharashtrian. A very versatile dish, poha can be prepared in numerous ways.
            The most common variant is kanda poha which is made with onions</item>
        <item>The much famed Ragda Patties or as the locals would name it Ragda ?pattice?
            (a localised version on the English ?patties?) is a part of Maharashtra\'s
            delicious street food that one should never leave out on. It is a yet another lip-smacking street
            food in Mumbai which is prepared by using curried dried peas and patties.</item>
        <item>Modak is one of the most famous sweet found in Maharashtra and is extensively
            eaten during the Ganesh Chaturthi Festival all around the state. The sweet
            filling on the inner part of a modak consists of freshly grated coconut and jaggery
            while the outer shell is made out of rice flour and is very soft.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="hotelName">
        <item>Taj Santacruz</item>
        <item>Conrad Pune Koregaon Park by Hilton</item>
        <item>Trident Bandra Kurla</item>
        <item>The Taj Mahal Tower Mumbai</item>
        <item>JW Marriott Mumbai Sahar Airport</item>
        <item>The St. Regis Mumbai</item>
        <item>JW Marriott Pune</item>
        <item>Marriott Suites Pune</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hotelImage">
        <item>https://q-cf.bstatic.com/images/hotel/max1280x900/576/57611845.jpg</item>
        <item>https://r-cf.bstatic.com/images/hotel/max1280x900/646/64676763.jpg</item>
        <item>https://live.staticflickr.com/7112/6857886644_f91d64e0dc_b.jpg</item>
        <item>https://live.staticflickr.com/1808/42924629761_080c7898b4_b.jpg</item>
        <item>https://q-cf.bstatic.com/images/hotel/max1280x900/249/249447463.jpg</item>
        <item>https://r-cf.bstatic.com/images/hotel/max1280x900/178/178789843.jpg</item>
        <item>https://q-cf.bstatic.com/images/hotel/max1280x900/248/248594195.jpg</item>
        <item>https://r-cf.bstatic.com/images/hotel/max1280x900/197/197973600.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hotelDescription">
        <item>Taj Santacruz is located in Santa Cruz at a 2-minute walk from the Chhatrapati
            Shivaji Domestic Airport and 2.5 mi from International terminal. The property
            is located 5 mi from the Andheri commercial hub, 5.6 mi from Bombay Exhibition Center
            (Goregaon) and 3.1 mi from the financial hub of Bandra Kurla complex.</item>
        <item>Featuring 6 dining options, an outdoor temperature controlled swimming pool and
            24- hour fitness center, Conrad Pune - Luxury by Hilton offers accommodations in Pune.
            Guests can enjoy a drink at the on-site bar.</item>
        <item>The 5-star Trident Bandra Kurla provides an outdoor swimming pool and full spa
            services. Concierge services and room service are available 24 hours.
            On-site parking is free. Complimentary WiFi is available in all rooms.</item>
        <item>Built in 1973, the iconic The Taj Mahal Tower Mumbai stands majestically across
            from the Gateway of India, overlooking the Arabian Sea. The Tower stands in
            harmonious contrast to The Taj Mahal Palace with its arched balconies and newly
            refurbished rooms. Sprawling over 2.6 acres, this luxurious hotel features 10
            restaurants and a variety of traditional Indian therapies at Jiva Spa.</item>
        <item>Located 400 m from Chhatrapati Shivaji International Airport Mumbai and offering
            an outdoor swimming pool, fitness center and a spa wellness center,
            JW Marriott Mumbai Sahar is located in Andheri East.</item>
        <item>With exquisitely styled and lavishly appointed accommodations, The St. Regis Mumbai
            is located in city’s premier entertainment and commercial district of Lower Pareland is renowned for
            its unique sense of refined luxury. Free WiFi is available.</item>
        <item>Offering 5-star rooms overlooking the city, JW Marriott Pune features a spa,
            pool with bar and a rooftop restaurant. Providing free parking, it has 8 dining options.
            The property features a spa with
            13 treatment rooms where the guests can head to for relaxation.</item>
        <item>Marriott Suites Pune is an all-suite pet-friendly hotel located in the Koregaon
            Park neighborhood. It is 3.4 mi from Pune International Airport, 3.2 mi from Phenix
            Market City Mall and a 15 minute drive away from IT hubs such as EON IT Park,
            Business Bay, Commerce Zone and Magarpatta Cyber city. It is also close to local
            attractions like Osho Ashram that is 1.5 mi away while Aga Khan Palace is 2.1 mi
            and Shaniwar Wada is 4.7 mi from the property</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="eventName">
        <item>Gudhi Padwa - The Harvest Festival</item>
        <item>Ganesh Chathurthi</item>
        <item>Krishna Janmashtami</item>
        <item>Makar Sankranti</item>
        <item>Bhau Beej</item>
        <item>Ashadhi Ekadashi</item>
        <item>Pola</item>
        <item> Shivaji Jayanti</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="eventImage">
        <item>https://www.myindiandream.in/upload/Gudhi_Padwa_-_Its_time_for_the_festivities_to_begin_1490778647.jpg</item>
        <item>https://storage.needpix.com/rsynced_images/lord-ganesha-3698062_1280.jpg</item>
        <item>https://previews.123rf.com/images/adsniks/adsniks1712/adsniks171200132/103781771-photograph-of-dahi-handi-on-gokulashtami-festival-in-india-which-is-lord-shri-krishna-s-birth-day.jpg</item>
        <item>https://st1.latestly.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/International-Kite-Festival-beautiful-pics.jpg</item>
        <item>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/thumb/msid-71795710,imgsize-356575,width-400,resizemode-4/71795710.jpg</item>
        <item>https://previews.agefotostock.com/previewimage/medibigoff/9305a6531a9cc66986feb2c520b2d374/dpa-sgg-150379.jpg</item>
        <item>https://www.holidify.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/Pola.jpg</item>
        <item>https://static.toiimg.com/photo/62996111.cms</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="eventDescription">
        <item>Gudhi Padwa signifies the beginning of a prosperous new year and Hindus consider
            it to be one of the most auspicious days. It falls on the first day of the Lunar
            calendar, marking the new year. It is celebrated with great pomp and show all over
            the state. Households are decorated with garlands and rangolis, and a gudhi
            is put up outside the home to welcome prosperity and good health in to the family</item>
        <item>YLord Ganesha, the deity of wisdom, is the most loved in Maharashtra and
            Ganesh Chaturthi is celebrated with the most grandeur. In August, preparations
            for the auspicious day when Lord Ganesh was born – begin with great enthusiasm.
            It is an 11-day festival, beginning with the installation of beautifully sculpted
            Ganesh idols in homes and large pandals, colorfully decorated, depicting religious and cultural themes.</item>
        <item>Gokul Ashtami or Janmashtami celebrates the birth of Lord Krishna. Devotees fast till midnight
            on the eve of the birth of Lord Krishna. Krishna-janma is celebrated at midnight at
            temples and in homes amidst bhajans (devotional songs), marking the birth of Lord Krishna.</item>
        <item>Also known as Uttarayan or Pongal in other parts of the country, Makar Sankranti is
            the celebration of the winter solstice. It is the celebration of the advent of spring, the day when
            the sun leaves the southern hemisphere and begins its journey in the northern hemisphere.</item>
        <item>Just as the country celebrates sibling love on Raksha Bandhan, this Festival of
            Maharashtra celebrates this special bond on one additional day. Celebrated on the fifth and final day of Diwali,
            it is a special celebration of the all the revelry and rivalry of this everlasting bond. </item>
        <item>Celebrated in honour of the great Hindu god Vishnu, Ashadhi Ekadashi is the
            culmination of the great Pandharpur chi Vari (Journey to Pandharpur). Pandharpur
            is a town in Maharashtra on the banks of the river Chandrabhaga and is considered
            to be the abode of Vitthal, a local form of the mighty God. Almost
            a month in advance, millions of people begin a pilgrimage to visit the holy
            city on foot.</item>
        <item>Like Lohri in North India, the harvest festival of Pola is celebrated by farmers
            all over Maharashtra. It falls on Pithori Amavasya, the new moon day of the holy
            month of Shravan. On this day bullocks, which are an integral part of the
            agriculture – basically the backbone of it – are worshiped.</item>
        <item>Chattrapati Shivaji Maharaj was the greatest ruler of Maharashtra. He was known
            for his courage and intelligence. He laid the foundation of a Hindu empire which
            lasted for over two centuries before the British took over. All Maharashtrians
            have great reverence
            and regard for him and his birthday is celebrated all across the state as Shivaji Jayanti.</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
